Hello friends, my name is Sachin, and
today I'm back with a new video for you.
Today, we're going to talk
about the Karuna Kavach policy.
Yes, friends, our
insurance regulator had
asked all insurance companies to
come up with an extension and helpline that
covers only Karuna. Other
health insurance policies are quite expensive for some people, as
they cover all illnesses.
However, in light of this pandemic,
IRDA has issued
instructions to everyone to come up with a plan
that includes the common
features and PMs of all companies. These policies are minimal, so that
people
can go to private hospitals for treatment and do
n't have to waste too much. So, friends,
today we're talking about this plan. I'll
explain
how to calculate the premium and
how to buy this policy. So,
before we proceed further, friends, if you're
new to my channel, please subscribe.
If you like this video,
please share it, because knowledge grows by sharing. So,
friends, let's learn about the benefits of this important plan.  Let us
know about this
plan. Here you will see that it
starts from Rs 3 lakh.
You will see that the plans of other companies
start from Rs 50,000, but
here it starts from Rs 3 lakh and
goes up to Rs 5 lakh and this multiple
increases with 50,000. Like, you can take the first plan of Til for Rs
3.5 lakh or you
can take the Chawla plan for Rs 4.5 lakh
or Rs 5 lakh. This option is available to you.
Talking about entries,
anyone between the age of 18 to 65 years can
take this plan.
If you want to add children in that plan, then
you can add children from two-one day old to one
year old
in this plan.
If we talk about such a family floater plan,
friends, there are three durations in it,
these are common in all the plans, three and a half months, six and a half months
and nine and a half months and it has two
initial waiting periods of 15 days
i.e. 15  If you get any corona disease within a day and are
found corona positive, then
half the
policy will not work in the first 15 days. It has been activated on the same day in this year,
so you should understand that it will
work only on the sixteenth day from the day your policy is made. If we talk about
road ambulance here, then the
maximum limit here is ₹2000, so you can take
₹2000 so that whatever donation you make for the entire year, you will be
able to take your ₹2000 only once. If we talk about
home treatment, then friends, the
facility of home treatment is available here. Here,
if the doctor writes to you that for the
fourth day you have to stay at home and
your treatment is possible at home, then also here you have to
subscribe to the company for your bills and medicine expenses, which you can get stopped. If we do
not discuss post graduation here, then the expenses of the first 15 days and
30 days of
yours, that is, if you are supposed to be
detected with corona  And even before that, if you have to take any
medicines and get the doctor's fees paid
and you have the bills for that, then you
can get it paid. Similarly, if you get
admitted and come home like this
and even after that you have to go to see the doctor for a few days
and some of the bills are for the expenses of medicines, then
you can get that done here for up to 30 days.
Talking about AYUSH treatment,
you will get that too here. If you are
given any Ayurvedic medicines,
Unani medicines,
Siddha treatment during your treatment in the hospital, then also you will
get the money for it.
Friends, here is an
optional crash benefit within the company, which if you are
hospitalized and if you have taken this plan, then
suppose you have taken a plan of Rs 5 lakhs
under this, then here
you will get 0.5% of it i.e. Rs 2500 per day, this is the
maximum limit for 15 days in the hospital for phone treatment, so if
you  If you
add this to your policy, you can also avail these benefits.
So friends, these are
some details of the plan benefits. And if you remember,
I made the last video on a strange thing. In that,
we covered the Corona Kavach
plan. So, I will give
you the link on the i button here. If you
want to see the HDFC plan, you
can go there and see it. So friends,
now let me explain to you how you can avail this policy. So, let's see.
And so friends, see, we have come here. On
one side,
I will give you the link to the HDFC website. In the description,
as soon as you click, you will be
redirected here. Whether you
want to avail this from your mobile, or
from your laptop or desktop,
you can avail this. Here, I am
showing you on my desktop how
you can avail this. So,
first of all, you will have to enter your name.
Here, I have entered my full name. Here, I will have to enter my
mobile number.
So, I will enter my mobile number.
Here,
I will enter my email address.  You will have to go here and
enter your email address
and here if you
want to receive any communication on WhatsApp,
after the policy is made, you will also get it on WhatsApp
and in the duty and communication, then you
check it and make a profit,
as soon as the process starts from here, your date
of birth will be asked here, so here we
enter our date of birth, that is,
this date of birth has to be entered, here you
can choose your set, I live in Delhi,
so I have selected Delhi here,
leave submit, see, go here, as
I told you that you can take any plan from 3 lakh to
5 lakh,
for example, we take four ways here, for
how many days plan do you want to take, here we
take a plan of 195, hospital
telecast, I told you that it is
optional, should you take it or not,
I am not taking it at the moment, so let's calculate the
premium, so here you have the premium
calculator,
you will have to pay Rs 2500 with GST, so we are doing it right here,
okay  If we do it on 2005 then
we will proceed with it, then
in the prostate itself it will first ask whether you
are an adult, then your data will go here, it is self,
you are taking a policy for this, you take a
selfie here, you will select the name here, you will
enter your full name,
here
I am asking whether you have any problem with the
West Indies, you do not have any disease, so
I will note it down
and enter it, so see
my details are filled here, we are being asked for his address,
so here you can enter your ad, it is turned
on, right,
enter the pin code, the state and
city will be selected automatically and if they are asking a question, then
you enter the salary in hand salary,
enter self-employed,
here you will be asked for the details of nomination, so
here you can enter the name of the nominee,
whoever is in your blood relation,
you enter their name here
and their date of birth will be asked here, so
you can enter the date of birth here, their date of birth was or is it, yes,
I have given this date  Date of birth, enter
constitution review, now all the details of your complete
form that you have submitted will be
here, that is 2,000 Aftab
premium Haider ₹5 Karuna's workshop,
without identifying this, you have taken your airplane, this is its
plan code, here its proposal number has come,
here the name has come and here you will see the
date of birth has come, it is
clearly written here for you that of widow's performance
here and your sum insured is
four lakh rupees and here it is clearly
written about the medical test guideline
that if anyone above 57 years of age
means any person purchases this policy, then there will be a
tele underwriting
medical, then you will have to see it or if
you have any disease, you have a
pre-existing disease, only then your medical can be done,
you have to set up the term and condition
and the same will ask about WhatsApp,
so increase the profit, this is it,
as soon as you increase the profit, you will
come to the payment page, there
are many options here like there is an option of wallet, now wallet  If you
select it,
you will get many options on Amazon on your phone. Similarly, if
you do it with credit card, then here
you will be asked for credit card details
and if you do it with debit card, then
SAM details of debit card will be asked. If you do it
with net banking, then here
you can use different banks from below. You
can make payment from the bank in which you have an account. Along with this,
you also have the option of UPI here. If
you have BHIM on Google, whatever you
can use on your phone, then you
can buy this policy by entering it here. So
friends, this was the Karuna
Kavach policy of robbery. If you liked this video,
then definitely share it with your friends
and subscribe to my channel.
Thank you very much for watching this video.